Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 3: General Administration Files, 1920-2008; (101 Boxes)
  - Subseries 3.1: Subject Files, 1920-1961; (48 Boxes)
    - Griffin, Rev. William M. - Director, Altoona, Pennsylvania, 1938-1940 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Griffith, Leo G. - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1923-1934 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Guilfoyle, Rt. Rev. Msgr. George H. - President, NCCC, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - H, 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - H, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - H, 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - H, 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - H, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - H, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - H, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - H, 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - H, 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - H, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - H, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - H, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - H, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - H, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - H, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - H (1), 1961 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - H (2), 1961 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Haas, Rt. Rev. Msgr. Francis J. - Washington, D.C., 1924-1935 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Hagerty, J.E. - Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio, 1924-1928 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Hanigen, Rev. Charles, 1924 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Hanley, James H. - City National Bank Building, Omaha, Nebraska, 1922-1932 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Hannon, Mary Regina - Honolulu, Territory of Hawaii, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Harahan, Catharine A. - Richmond, Virginia, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Harlan, Laura White House, D.C., 1922 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      Contains Pres. Harding's Letter
    - Harrisburg Meeting - Material (1), 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Harrisburg Meeting - Material (2), 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Harrison, Shelby M., 1923 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Harty, Most Rev. James J., 1922-1924 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Hayes, Rev. Edward A. - Ossining, New York, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Advisory Council on Child Welfare Services, 1958-1960 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children Welfare Services - Discussions and Meetings of Directors of Catholic Charities (1), 1950-1954 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children Welfare Services - Discussions and Meetings of Directors of Catholic Charities (2), 1950-1954 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children Welfare Services, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children's Bureau - Extension of Aid to Dependent Children, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children's Bureau - Report of Survey - Delinquency Treatment Needs in Some States, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children's Bureau - Juvenile Delinquency, 1952-1955 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Children's Bureau - Juvenile Delinquency - Conference June 28-30, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Federal Council on Aging, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - National Conference on Homemaker and Related Services Jan. 27, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Meeting with Secretary Folsom, 1956-1959 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - National Conference on Nursing Homes and Homes for the Aging Washington, Feb. 25-28, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Interfaith Groups - November 1959 Meeting - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Interfaith Meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Interfaith Meetings, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - Public Health Service Report, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of - "A New Look at Child Welfare Services" Statement, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Health/Medical - Committee on Costs of Medical Care, 1928-1931 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Health/Medical - Technical Committee on Medical Care, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Health/Medical - Health and Hospital Survey - St. Louis, Missouri, ca. 1934 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Health/Medical - Interdepartmental Committee to Coordinate Health and Welfare Activities, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Health/Medical - Hospital Bills, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Health/Medical - Health Survey - Baltimore, Maryland, ca. 1934 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Health/Medical - Healthcare - Children, 1936-1939 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Health/Medical - Miscellaneous Health Studies (1), 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Health/Medical - Miscellaneous Health Studies (2), 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Health/Medical - Tax Funds Received by Catholic Hospitals, 1938 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Health/Medical - Diocesan Hospitals, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Health/Medical - Hospital Survey - Father Bell, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Health/Medical - Child Welfare Study (Forms A, B) - Letter November 24, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Health/Medical - Child Care, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Health/Medical - Dependent Children - Boarding Homes, 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Health/Medical - Psychiatric Group Material - Drs. Dunn and Briefs, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Health/Medical - Children's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Health/Medical - Mental Hygiene, 1933-1935 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Health/Medical - Child Welfare Study and Correspondence (1), 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Health/Medical - Child Welfare Study and Correspondence (2), 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Health/Medical - Child Welfare Study and Correspondence (3), 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Health/Medical - Community Chest Participants, ca. 1927 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Hefner, Miss Helen, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Heide, Henry, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Helmann, Very Rev. Msgr. M.W. - Lincoln, Nebraska, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Henderson, Sophie, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Heneghan, George E., President, St. Louis, Missouri, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Heneghan, George E., President, Superior Council, SVDP, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Hennerty, William J., 1922 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Hennerty, William J., 1923-1925 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Hickey, Rev. Augustine F., 1924 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Hickey, Rt. Rev. Thomas F., 1925 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Hierarchy, Correspondence with, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Higgins, Daniel Paul - New York City, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Highlander Folk School (1), 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Highlander Folk School (2), 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Highlander Folk School, 1958-1959 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Highway Commission, 1931-1939 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Historical Data (1), 1948-1956 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Historical Data (2), 1948-1956 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Historical, 1959-1961 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Hoban, Rt. Rev. Michael J., 1923, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Holland, Hon. Rush L., 1924 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Holy Year - Charity Exhibit, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Homes for Incurables, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Homes for Working Boys - Clubs for Older Boys, ca. 1946 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Homes and Shelters for Homeless Men, Boys, and Women, ca. 1940 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Hooper, Bertha Freeman, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Hopkins, Harry (Administrator, Federal Emergency Relief Administration - Washington, D.C., 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Hospitals - Special Types 9Mental - Nervous Cases, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (1), 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (2), 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (3), 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (4), 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (5), 1937-1942 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - House Committee Investigating National Defense Immigration - Committee to Investigate Interstate Migration of Destitute Citizens (6), 1937-1942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Houses of the Good Shepherd, 1934, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Housing, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Housing, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Housing Legal Digest, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Howes, Rev. Robert G. - Relocation, 1959-1964 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - "Housing in Our Time" in San Antonio, Texas - Pictorial Supplement to the 1939 Annual Report, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Howley, Rev. Richard T. - San Francisco, California, 1936-1939 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Hughes, Margaret M., 1946-1947 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Human Betterment Association, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Hughes, Rt. Rev. Msgr. William, Director, Catholic Indian Missions - Washington, D.C., 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Hunt, Mrs. Sara F., 1923 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - I, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - I, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - I, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - I, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - I, 1951-1953 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - I, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - I, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - I, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - I, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - I, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Immigration Meeting - NCWC - December 19, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Immigration Meeting - NCWC - March 27, 1957-1958 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Indian Missions - Need of Relief, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Indian Missions - Work with Catholic Indians - Sr. Providencia, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation (1), 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation (2), 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Industrials Area Foundation, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Industrial Schools, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Infant Asylums and Maternity Hospitals, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Institute for Religious and Social Studies, 1953-1956 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Institute for Religious and Social Studies, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Institutions, Classified List of, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Institutions - Expenditures of Charitable Institutions - Material Collected for Mr. Montavon, 1941-1942 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Institutions - Child-Caring Institutions, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Institutions - Child-Caring Institutions with Lay Teachers or Assistants, ca. 1940 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Institutions - Institutions for Dependent Colored Children, ca. 1940 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Institutions - Institutions for Mental and Nervous Patients, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Institutions - Institutions for Mentally Handicapped Children, 1939-1953 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Institutions - Institutions for Physically Handicapped Children, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Institutions - Institutions for the Aged, ca. 1940 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Inter-Faith Cooperation in Social Welfare, 1953-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Interior, Department of, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - International Conference of Catholic Charities - Community Development - Msgr. John O'Grady, VP, 1958-1960 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - International Conference of Social Work - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - International Conference of Social Work - Correspondence (1), 1949-1956 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - International Conference of Social Work - Correspondence (2), 1949-1956 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - International Conference of Social Work - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - International Health Conference, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - International Meeting - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - International Social Welfare - Correspondence (1), 1946-1950 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - International Social Welfare - Correspondence (2), 1946-1950 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - International Social Welfare - Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Interstate Commission on Crime - Newark, New Jersey, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - J, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - J, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - J, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - J, 1948-1950 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - J, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - J, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - J, 1958-1959 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - J, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Jacobi, Rev. H. Joseph - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Jacobi, Rt. Rev. H. Joseph - President, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1948-1949 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Japanese Embassy, 1923 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Jennings, Mary, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Joint Vocational Service, Inc. - New York City (1), 1933-1938 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Joint Vocational Service, Inc. - New York City (2), 1933-1938 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Joint Vocational Service, Inc. - New York City (1), 1939 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Joint Vocational Service, Inc. - New York City (2), 1939 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Miss Caroline W, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Juvenile Delinquency, 1938-1943 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - K, 1922-1925 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - K, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - K, 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - K, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - K, 1946-1947 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - K, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - K, 1948-1950 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - K, 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - K, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - K, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - K, 1958-1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - K, 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - K, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kane, Rev. Francis J., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Keane, Rev. William C. - Director, Catholic Charities - Albany, New York, 1923-1939 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Keane, Rev. William C. - Albany, New York, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Keasey, Sr. M. Boniface, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Keating, Val M. - San Antonio, Texas, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Keegan, Rt. Rev. Msgr. Robert F. - New York City, 1921-1925 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Keegam, Rt. Rev. Msgr. Robert F. - New York City, 1926-1927 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Keegan, Rt. Rev. Msgr. Robert F. - New York City, 1928-1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Keegan, Rt. Rev. Msgr. Robert F. - New York City, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Keeler, Floyd, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Keeler, Hon. Oscar E., 1924 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Kelley, Most Rev. Francis C. - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1933-1935 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Kelly, Bessie, 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Kelly, Rev. C.F., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Kelly, Rt. Rev. Edward D., 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Kelly, Edmund J., 1925 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Kelly, Miss Kitty, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Kelly, Mrs. Mary Kate, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Kelly, Nora, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Kelly, Mr. W.J., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Kelty, James F., S.T.L., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Kenkel, Frederick P. - Catholic Central Verein of America - St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1934 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Kennedy, James F. - Chicago, Illinois, 1922-1931 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Kennedy, Walter B., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Kenny, Rev. Michael, S.J., 1923, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Kerby, Rev. Dr. William J. - Washington, D.C., 1922-1928 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Kerby, Rev. Dr. William J. - Washington, D.C., 1929-1936 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Kerby Guild, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Kernahan, W.J., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Keys, Miss May, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - King, Miss Anne, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Kingsley, Mr. Sherman C., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Kirk, Harry J., 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Klein, Philip - New York School of Social Work - New York City, 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Korenchan, Fr. William - Columban Father at United Nations, 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Krmpotic, Msgr. M.D., 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Kublmen, Rev. A.J., S.J., 1923 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - L, 1922-1929 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - L, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - L, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - L, 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - L, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - L, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - L, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - L, 1948-1950 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - L, 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - L, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - L, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - L, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - L, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Labaree, Mary S. - Children's Bureau, Department of Labor - Washington, D.C., 1923-1935 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Labor, US Department of - Bureau of Labor Statistics and Standards (1), 1939-1942 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Labor, US Department of - Bureau of Labor Statistics and Standards (2), 1939-1942 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Labor, US Department of - Bureau of Labor Statistics and Standards (3), 1939-1942 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Labor, US Department of - Bureau of Labor Statistics and Standards (4), 1939-1942 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Labor, US Department of - Bureau of Labor Statistics and Standards (5), 1939-1942 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1923-1939 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1933 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1936-1937 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau, 1941-1943 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - "The States and Child Labor,", 1920 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Tables for Fields other than Family Welfare (March), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Reports other than Family Welfare (April), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Reports other than Family Welfare (May), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Reports other than Family Welfare (June), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Fields other than Family Welfare (July), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Tables other than Family Welfare (August), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Schedules other than Family Welfare (September), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Tables other than Family Welfare (October), 1931 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Labor, US Department of - Children's Bureau - Workmen's Compensation and Rehabilitation - Conference, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Ladies of Charity, 1934-1945 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Ladies of Charity, 1951-1960 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Laffey, Mrs. Margaret E., 1923 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Lapp, Dr. John A. - Petroleum Labor Policy Board, Department of Interior, 1922-1936 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Larkin, Rev. Paschal, O.M.C.A.P., 1924 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Larkin, Dr. Thomas E., 1924-1929 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Larkins, Dr. Thomas E. - Anthracite Board of Conciliation - Hazelton, Pennsylvania, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Larmour, Miss Victoria, 1923-1929 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Laughlin, Anne, N.Y.A. - Topeka, Kansas, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Laughlin, Sara E. - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1922-1924 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Laughlin, Sara E. - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1925-1939 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Laughnane, Miss Anne, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Leahy, Dr. Sylvester R., 1924-1925 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - LeBarbier, Adele, 1921-1922 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1922-1939 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1945-1946 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - LeBlond, Most Rev. C. Hubert, Bishop of St. Louis, Missouri, 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - LeBuffe, Rev. Francis P., Fordham School of Social Service - New York City, 1924-1926 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Lennon, Rev. John J., 1951 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Lennon, Rev. John J., 1954 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Leonard, Rev. Edwin L. - Baltimore, Maryland, 1923-1929 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Leonard, Rev. Edwin L. - Baltimore, Maryland, 1930-1937 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Lewis, Mr. Francis J., KSG - Chicago, Illinois, 1923-1931 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Library, 1949-1951 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Loftus, Rev. Eugene A. - Buffalo, New York, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Lucey, Most Rev. Robert E. - Amarillo, Texas, 1923-1936 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Lundberg, Miss Emma O. - Children's Bureau, Department of Labor - Washington, D.C., 1923-1932 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Lurie, H.L. - Bureau of Jewish Social Services, 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Lynch, Miss Marie - St. Louis, Missouri, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Lynch, Marie - Mt. Pocono, Pennsylvania, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Lynch, Rev. Edward J., 1922-1924 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - M, 1940-1942 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - M, 1943-1944 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - M, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - M, 1948-1950 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - M, 1951-1953 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - M, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - M, 1955-1956 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - M, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - M, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - M, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - MAC, 1922-1927 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - MAC, 1930-1933 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - MAC, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - MAC, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - MAC, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - MC, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - MC, 1943-1944 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - MC, 1944-1946 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - MC, 1948-1950 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - MC, 1950-1953 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - MC, 1954-1956 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - MC, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - MC, 1957-1958 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - MC, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - MC, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - ME, MI, MO, MY, 1922-1924 (Box 34, Folder 42)